bespokepost.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Bespoke Post

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of nabfly, Inc, doing business as Bespoke Post ("we", "our" or "us") on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on bespokepost.com (the "Site") and the services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively with the Site, the "Services"). We receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) if you register for the Site and the Services, through your user account on the Services (your "Account"); (ii) your use of the Services generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. The Services are not available to individuals under 18 years of age. The Site and Services are intended for users who access the Site from the United States or Canada.

What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") gathered when you are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications ("Third Party Services") that you elect to access through the Service or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

What Information Do We Collect?

In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we collect some of your Personal Information. One goal in collecting Personal Information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your Personal Information to:

  * help make this Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once;
  * help you quickly find information, products, and services;
  * help us create content on this Site that is most relevant to you;
  * alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer; and
  * deliver you the most awesome box possible.

We may use your Personal Information to enable you to interact directly with the Services, to customize your subscription, to send you information about our Services, to improve the content of the Services, to continue to operate the Services, and to customize the advertising and content that you receive. We collect the following types of information from our users:

User Content

Some features of the Services allow you to provide content to the Services, such as written comments. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your Account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties in a manner that does not reveal Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

Age

We respect children's privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. Elsewhere on this Site, you have represented and warranted that you are either 18 years of age. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you.

User Supplied Information

Some features of the Services may give you the option to request information, complete surveys or otherwise interact with us and our partners. We may collect information you provide in connection with your profile such as, but not limited to, your likes, dislikes, profession, hobbies, gender, age, and location. Information that you supply in connection with the Services is solely at your discretion. If you do supply Personal Information in response to such requests, we may use it for the purposes stated in that feature of the Services.

Financial and Account Information

When you create an Account, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username, password, email address, shipping and billing address(es), mobile phone number, and credit card number. This type of Personal Information is used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our site, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, we use the Personal Information to contact you. We do not currently store financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information); that information is stored by our third party payment processing company (the "Payment Processor"), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor's applicable terms of service and privacy policy.

IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically

We automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Services, including your IP address, location, browser or mobile platform, cookie information, and page information you requested. This information is used to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services (e.g., what links you have clicked on).

We treat this information as non-Personal information, except where required to do so by applicable law. In addition, the Services automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site. We collect information about devices accessing the Services, including type of device, which operating system is used, device settings, application IDs, and unique device identifiers. We may also use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to determine how often individuals use parts of the Services so that we can analyze and improve them.

Email Communications

You may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our customer service and to provide you with access to the Services as necessary. As part of the Services, you will also receive emails and other communications from us relating to your Account, your subscription, and deliveries you have ordered. We may also occasionally send you marketing emails about the Services that we offer. We will never sell your email address to a third party without your permission.

Information Collected Using Cookies

Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize the mobile or web browser, and to tell us how and when you visit the Site and otherwise use the Services through the Internet. Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Services and may associate that information with your Account if you have one.

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave cookies active, because they enable you to take advantage of the most attractive features of the Services.

Ads appearing on the Service may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer. This information allows third parties to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. You may opt out of these advertisements, but please keep in mind that if you do so you will not fully be able to access the Services.

Information Related to Advertising and the Use of Web Beacons

To support and enhance the Services, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties advertisements, through the Services. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third party companies who engage with our user base as well as "ad networks." Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms.

Advertisements may be served through the Services to users through targeted advertisements to users who fit a certain general profile category and may be based on anonymized information inferred from information provided to us by a user, including Personal Information (e.g., gender or age), may be based on the Services usage patterns of particular users, or may be based on your activity on Third Party Services.

To increase the effectiveness of ad delivery, we may deliver a file (known as a web beacon) from an ad network to you through the Services. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit other websites. Because your mobile or web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network's servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

Aggregate Information

We collect statistical information about how both unregistered and registered users, collectively, use the Services ("Aggregate Information"). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information. This statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account or your web browser.

How, and With Whom, Is My Information Shared?

The Services are designed to provide you with desirable content and special offers through our Services.

Public Information about Your Activity on the Services

Some of your activity on and through the Services is public by default. This may include, but is not limited to, content you have posted publicly on the Site or otherwise through the Services.

Please also remember that if you choose to provide Personal Information using certain public features of the Services, then that information is governed by the privacy settings of those particular features and may be publicly available. Individuals reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines may index that information. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or information that you submit through the Services.

IP Address Information

While we collect and store IP address information, that information is not made public. We do at times, however, share this information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business, and as otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy.

Information You Elect to Share

You may use certain features of the Services to respond to advertisers, request information, purchase products or services, respond to surveys, enter contests, surveys or sweepstakes, or for other purposes. We may use information that you elect to provide for the purposes stated at the time of submission.

You may access other Third Party Services through the Services, for example by clicking on links to those Third Party Services from within the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these Third Party Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Party Services' privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Services.

Aggregate Information

We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use our Services and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how our Services interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non Personal Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.

Email Communications with Us

As part of the Services, you may occasionally receive email and other communications from us, such as communications relating to your Account. Communications relating to your Account will only be sent for purposes important to the Services, such as password recovery. We may also occasionally send you marketing emails about the Services; you may opt-out or unsubscribe from receiving such emails through your Account settings.

User Profile Information

User profile information including your username and other information you publicly post on the Site may be displayed to other users. We will not directly reveal user email addresses to other users.

Financial Information

As stated above, we do not currently store financial information, as that information is stored by our Payment Processor. However, we may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information from our Payment Processor for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Services, protecting against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

Information Shared with our Partners and Agents

In addition to the data sharing described above, we enter into relationships with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses sell items or provide promotions to you through our Services. We may also provide the Services in conjunction with our partners' business offerings. We will make it clear when one of our partners is associated with a transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that business if we have your permission to do so.

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our "Agents"). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide the Services to you. For example, we partner with third parties (such as the United Parcel Service) to ship products, to ensure delivery, and so that we can obtain feedback, improve the quality of our service, and measure and improve the quality of the service of the third party. In the example of shippers, we provide them some Personal Information such as your name, shipping address, email, and phone number. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents.

Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others

also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as it reasonably believes is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce theTerms of Serviceother user policies and agreements, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.

Information We Share With Your Consent

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

Is Information About Me Secure?

Your Account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your Account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.

We seek to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

We otherwise store all of our information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard techniques. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you that we store, Personal Information or otherwise.

International Users

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the Site is hosted on our computer servers in the United States. Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in the United States. As a result, United States federal and state governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through laws applicable in the United States. Your use of this site or the Service or your submission of any Personal Information to us will constitute your consent to the transfer of your Personal Information outside of your home country, including the United States, which may provide for different data protection rules than in your country.

What Information of Mine Can I Access?

If you are a registered user, you can access information associated with your Account by logging into the Services. Registered and unregistered users can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings.

California Privacy Rights: Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 151 W 25th St, Fl 5, New York, NY 10001.

What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?

You can always opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of the Services.

You can delete your Account by emailing [accounts@bespokepost.com.](mailto:accounts@bespokepost.com) Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account, and activity you provided us or posted on the Site prior to deletion will remain stored by us and may be publicly accessible. 

What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Services or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, please send us a detailed message to [legal@bespokepost.com.](mailto:legal@bespokepost.com) We will make every effort to resolve your concerns. 

Effective Date: June 28, 2018
